Marietta Simpson Collection, 1967-2019 SC 168
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 5. Programs
  - 5.1. Simpson Concerts and Recitals, 1975-2019, undated
    - Bach: St. Matthew Passion, Orchestra of St. Luke's, 1996-04-02 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess (Maria), Houston Grand Opera at Teatro alla Scala, 1996-07-17 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Mozart: Requiem; Stravinsky: Symphony of Psalms, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1996-08-24 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Thompson/Stein: Four Saints in Three Acts (Commère), Houston Grand Opera, Royal Scottish National Orchestra, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, 1996-09 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Handel: Messiah, Minnesota Orchestra, 1996-08 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - 14th Annual Concert for Peace, Farewell Tribute to Rev. James Parks Morton, 1996-12-31 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Recitals, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Schubert: Erlkönig; All-Schubert Program, New York Philharmonic, 1997-01-1997-02 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Moses Hogan Chorale, 1997-01-05 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 2, New Haven Symphony Orchestra, 1997-01-09 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, Robert Shaw Choral Workshop, 1997-01-19 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Witness, Plymouth Music Series, 1997-02-07 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Great Opera Choruses, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 1997-02-22 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Brahms: Alto Rhapsody, Fairfield Orchestra, 1997-03 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Remembering the Art of Marian Anderson, 1997-04 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 2, Harrisburg Symphony Orchestra, 1997-04 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Recital, Unity Concerts of New Jersey, 1997-05-11 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess, Bregenzer Festspiele, 1997-07 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Barber: Prayers of Kierkegaard; Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1997-08-24 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - French Connection, Ocean City Pops Orchestra, 1997-09-21 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 3, Madison Symphony Orchestra, 1997-10 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, New Jersey Symphony Orchestra, 1997-10-21 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Vaughan Williams: Serenade to Music, National Symphony Orchestra, 1997-10-25 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, City of Birmingham Symphony Orchestra, 1997-10-29 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Recital, Schubert and Brahms Festival, Library of Congress, 1997-11-18 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Handel: Messiah, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1997-12 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Stuttgarter Gala-Abend Georges' Christmas Party, 1997-12 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Handel: Messiah, Music Ministry of Metropolitan Baptist Church, 1997-12-21 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Recitals, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Szymanowski: Stabat Mater, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1998-01 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Cleveland Orchestra, 1998-02 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Bach: Magnificat, Orff: Carmina Burana, Philadelphia Orchestra, 1998-02 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1998-03 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, San Francisco Symphony, 1998-04 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Orchestra of St. Luke's, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra Chorus, 1998-04-03 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Vocal Quartet Recital, 1998-04-17 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Singing City Choir 50th Anniversary Concert, 1998-05-05 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - 66th Annual Bach Festival, Baldwin-Wallace College, 1998-05 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Marlboro School of Music Concerts, 1998-07-1998-08 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Beethoven: Mass in C, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1998-07-05 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Penderecki: Credo (world premiere), Oregon Bach Festival, 1998-07-11 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess (Maria), BBC Proms, 1998-08-01 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Cleveland Orchestra, Blossom Festival, 1998-08-28 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Beethoven: Missa Solemnis, National Symphony Orchestra, Beethoven Festival, 1998-09 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Tri-Cities Opera, 50th Anniversary Gala, 1998-09-19 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Penderecki: Credo, Internationalen Bachakademien, Stuttgart, 1998-10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Beethoven: Folksongs from the British Isles, Symphony No. 9, New York Philharmonic, 1998-10 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Penderecki: Credo, Krzysztof Penderecki Festival, 1998-10-05 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Handel: Messiah, Philharmonic Orchestra of New Jersey, 1998-12-01 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Spirit of Christmas, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 1998-12-11 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Handel: Messiah, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 1998-12 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Concert, Bach Choir of Bethlehem, 1998-12-05 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Christmas Concert, Bach Choir of Bethlehem, Bach Festival of Philadelphia, 1998-12-07 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Brahms: Liebeslieder-Walzer, Celebration of Benita Valente, 1999-01-14 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Verdi: Stabat Mater; Szymanowski: Stabat Mater; Poulenc: Stabat Mater, Carnegie Hall Choral Workshop, Orchestra of St. Luke's, 1999-01-17 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Robert Shaw Celebration, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1999-01-29 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Saint Paul Chamber Orchestra, 1999-02 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Music of William Grant Still, Coro Allegro, 1999-02-21 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Moses Hogan Chorale, St. Louis Cathedral Concerts, 1999-02-26 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Moses Hogan Chorale, Los Angeles Master Chorale, 1999-02-28 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Moses Hogan Chorale, Cleveland State University, 1999-10-09 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Memorial Mass for Claire Sprague Fixler, 1999-08 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Marian Anderson tribute, Cheyney University Center for Cultural Enrichment and Appreciation, 1999-03-11 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Evening of Classical Music, Harlem Dowling-West Side Center for Children and Family Services, 1999-02-22 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, Milwaukee Symphony Orchestra, 1999-03 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Beethoven: Missa Solemnis, Columbus Symphony Orchestra, 1999-03 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Shostakovich: Eleven Songs from Jewish Folk Poetry, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society Players, 1999-03-08 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Mendelssohn Club of Philadelphia, 1999-03-14 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Recital, Tuesday Musical Club Concert Series, Cleveland Orchestra, 1999-04-18 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Bach and Gospel Jubilee, Bach Festival of Philadelphia, 1999-04-25 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 1999-06 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Weill: The Road of Promise (Ruth), Plymouth Music Series of Minnesota, 1999-06-03 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 2, Grant Park Symphony Orchestra, Grant Park Music Festival, 1999-07 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Mahler: Kindertotenlieder, Mezinárodní Hudební Festival, 1999-09-21 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Bach Choir of Bethlehem, Bach Festival Orchestra, 1999-10-04 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Temple University Concert Choir, 1999-10-29 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Tippett: A Child of Our Time (Aunt), Kansas City Symphony, 1999-11 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 1999-11 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Collegiate Chorale, 1999-11-16 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Handel: Messiah, Musica Sacra Chorus and Orchestra, 1999-12 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Handel: Messiah, Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra, 1999-12 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Bach: Cantata BWV 200; Pergolesi: Stabat Mater, Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 1999-12 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Copland: Old American Songs, Colorado Symphony Orchestra, 2000-01-06 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Recital, Carson-Newman College Concert-Lecture Series, 2000-01-20 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Bach Choir of Philadelphia, Carnegie Hall, 2000-02-07 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Mozart: Coronation Mass; Requiem, Voices of Ascension Chorus and Orchestra, Lincoln Center, 2000-02-24 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Shostakovich: Eleven Songs from Jewish Folk Poetry, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society Players, 2000-03-08 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Pergolesi: Stabat Mater, Handel and Haydn Society, 2000-03 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Brahms: Alto Rhapsody; Beethoven: Choral Fantasy; Mozart: Requiem, Mendelssohn Club of Philadelphia, 2000-03-26 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bach: St. John Passion, New York Philharmonic, 2000-04 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Bach: St. Matthew Passion, Cleveland Orchestra, 2000-04 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, 2000-05 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Ravel: L'enfant et les Sortilèges, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 2000-05 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 8, Dallas Symphony Orchestra, 2000-05 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Ravel: L'enfant et les Sortilèges, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Libbey Bowl (Ojai, CA), 2000-06-02 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Cleveland Orchestra, 2000-07 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Elgar: Dream of Gerontius, Springfield Symphony Orchestra (Berkshire Choral Festival), 2000-08-05 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Dvořák: Stabat Mater, Houston Symphony Orchestra, 2000-09 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Janacêk: Glagolitic Mass, Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra, Prague Philharmonic Choir, 2000-09 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, 2000-10 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 2000-10 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Handel: Messiah, Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 2000-12 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Handel: Messiah, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2000-12 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Bach Choir of Bethlehem and Festival Orchestra (Meiji-En, Philadelphia, PA), 2001-06-26 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Musical Performance, GHS Class of 220 25th Year Reunion, 2001-11-24 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Moses Hogan Singers, St. Francis of Assisi Church, Ann Arbor, MI, 2001-01-10 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Moses Hogan Singers, Oberlin College Artist Recital Series and Convocation, 2001-02-06 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Janacêk: Glagolitic Mass, Cleveland Orchestra, 2001-01 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 3, Columbus Symphony Orchestra, 2001-01 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Tribute to Martin Luther King, Jr., Hilton Head Orchestra, 2001-01-15 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Beethoven: Missa Solemnis, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, 2001-02 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2001-03-2001-04 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Prokofiev: Alexander Nevsky, Lexington Philharmonic (Notre Dame Basilica), 2001-04-06 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Dvořák: Stabat Mater, Orchestra Symphonique de Montréal, 2001-04-11 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Stravinsky: Pulcinella, Berliner Sinfonie Orchester, 2001-04 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Kansas City Symphony, 2001-05 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Bernstein: Symphony No. 1, Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, 2001-09-21 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Mozart: Requiem, St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, 2001-10 (Box: 12, Folder 1)
    - Shostakovich: Eleven Songs from Jewish Folk Poetry, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2001-10 (Box: 12, Folder 2)
    - Bach and Gospel Jubilee, Bach Festival of Philadelphia, 2001-10-21 (Box: 12, Folder 3)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Princeton Pro Musica, 2001-10-28 (Box: 12, Folder 4)
    - Mozart: Requiem, San Antonio Symphony, 2001-11 (Box: 12, Folder 5)
    - Handel: Messiah, Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 2001-11-2001-12 (Box: 12, Folder 6)
    - Handel: Messiah, Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 2001-12 (Box: 12, Folder 7)
    - Handel: Messiah, Metropolitan Baptist Church, 2001-12-16 (Box: 12, Folder 8)
    - Bach: Cantata BWV 27; Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, New York Philharmonic, 2001-12-31 (Box: 12, Folder 9)
    - Recital, Detroit Public Library, 2002-02-13 (Box: 12, Folder 10)
    - Recital, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society, 2002-02-13 (Box: 12, Folder 10)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 3, Grand Rapids Symphony, 2002-02 (Box: 12, Folder 11)
    - Hannibal Lokumbe: God, Mississippi, and a Man Called Evers (Myrlie Evers), New Jersey Symphony Orchestra, 2002-03 (Box: 12, Folder 12)
    - Undine Smith Moore: Scenes from the Life of a Martyr, Detroit Symphony Orchestra, 2002-03 (Box: 12, Folder 13)
    - Weber: Oberon (Puck), Collegiate Chorale, Orchestra of St. Luke's (Carnegie Hall), 2002-04-23 (Box: 12, Folder 14)
    - Beethoven: Missa Solemnis, Dallas Symphony Orchestra, 2002-05 (Box: 12, Folder 15)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Singing City 54th Anniversary Concert (Bryn Mawr, PA), 2002-05-04 (Box: 12, Folder 16)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Greenville Symphony Orchestra, 2002-05-18 (Box: 12, Folder 17)
    - Bruckner: Te Deum; Penderecki: Credo, Oregon Bach Festival, 2002-07-14 (Box: 12, Folder 18)
    - Bruckner: Te Deum; Penderecki: Credo, Sixth World Symposium on Choral Music (Minneapolis), 2002-08-08 (Box: 12, Folder 19)
    - September 11th Observance (Kimmel Center, Philadelphia), 2002-09-11 (Box: 12, Folder 20)
    - Ravel: L'enfant et les Sortilèges, Berlin Philharmonic, 2002-09 (Box: 12, Folder 21)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Lehigh University Choral Arts, 2002-10 (Box: 12, Folder 22)
    - Handel: Messiah, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2002-12 (Box: 12, Folder 23)
    - Recital, Rivercenter (Columbus, GA), 2003-11-15 (Box: 12, Folder 24)
    - Homegoing Service for Florence L. Bryant (St. Peter Missionary Baptist Church, Newark, NJ), 2003-12-22 (Box: 12, Folder 24)
    - Bernstein: Ain't got no tears left; Lonely me; Screwed on wrong; Big stuff, Pacific Symphony Orchestra, 2003-01-28 (Box: 12, Folder 25)
    - Bolcom: Songs of Innocence and of Experience, Pacific Symphony Orchestra, 2003-02-03 (Box: 12, Folder 25)
    - Brahms: Zwei Gesäng op. 91; other vocal works, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society, 2003-02-16 (Box: 12, Folder 26)
    - R. Strauss: vocal music; spirituals, Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, 2003-02-26 (Box: 12, Folder 27)
    - Mozart: Requiem, Flint Symphony Orchestra, 2003-04-12 (Box: 12, Folder 28)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 3, Colorado Symphony Orchestra, 2003-05-2003-06 (Box: 12, Folder 29)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Memphis Symphony Orchestra, 2003-05-03 (Box: 12, Folder 30)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Philadelphia Orchestra, 2003-05-07 (Box: 12, Folder 31)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, Cincinnati May Festival, 2003-05-17 (Box: 12, Folder 32)
    - Brahms: Alto Rhapsody, UCI Symphony Orchestra, UC Irvine, 2003-06 (Box: 13, Folder 1)
    - Master Class, Chancellor's Distinguished Fellows Series, UC Irvine, 2003-06 (Box: 13, Folder 1)
    - Bishop Kenneth H. Moales 50th Anniversary (Washington, DC), 2003-08-05 (Box: 13, Folder 2)
    - Blitzstein: Regina (Addie), Lyric Opera of Chicago, 2003-09-2003-10 (Box: 13, Folder 3)
    - Bach: Cantata BWV 140; Magnificat; Cantata BWV 63, Bach Choir of Bethlehem, Bach Festival Orchestra, 2003-12 (Box: 13, Folder 4)
    - Handel: Messiah, American Bach Soloists (UC Davis), 2003-12-12 (Box: 13, Folder 5)
    - Handel: Messiah, Shiloh Baptist Church (Washington, DC), 2003-12-14 (Box: 13, Folder 6)
    - Szymanowski: Stabat Mater, Vienna Philharmonic, 2004-01-14 (Box: 13, Folder 7)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 3, Xalapa Symphony Orchestra (Veracruz, Mexico), 2004-01 (Box: 13, Folder 8)
    - Szymanowski: Stabat Mater, Berlin Philharmonic, 2004-02 (Box: 13, Folder 9)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Chicago Symphony Orchestra, 2004-02 (Box: 13, Folder 10)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Tucson Symphony Orchestra, 2004-04 (Box: 13, Folder 11)
    - Bolcom: Songs of Innocence and of Experience, University of Michigan School of Music, 2004-04-08 (Box: 13, Folder 12)
    - Currier: Gaian Variations, Brooklyn Philarhmonic (World premiere), 2004-04-21 (Box: 13, Folder 13)
    - Brahms: Alto Rhapsody, Colorado Symphony Orchestra, 2004-10 (Box: 13, Folder 14)
    - Bach: Mass in B Minor, Washington Chorus and Orchestra (Kennedy Center), 2004-11-21 (Box: 13, Folder 15)
    - Bach: Christmas Oratorio, Bach Choir of Bethlehem, 2004-12 (Box: 13, Folder 16)
    - Handel: Messiah, Philadelphia Orchestra (2 copies), 2004-12 (Box: 13, Folder 17)
    - Beethoven: Symphony 9, New York Philharmonic, 2004-12-31 (Box: 13, Folder 18)
    - Recital, Dunwoody United Methodist Church (Dunwoody, GA), 2005-03-18 (Box: 13, Folder 19)
    - Freedom Recital, May Festival 2005 (Cincinnati, OH), 2005-05-21 (Box: 13, Folder 19)
    - Memorial service, Barbara Mae Barrow Jacobs, Bay United Methodist Church (OH), 2005-12-03 (Box: 13, Folder 19)
    - The Art of Seduction, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2005-01-08 (Box: 13, Folder 20)
    - Menotti: The Medium (Madame Flora), Tri-Cities Opera, 2005-02 (Box: 13, Folder 21)
    - Blitzstein: Regina (Addie), Kennedy Center Opera, 2005-03 (Box: 13, Folder 22)
    - Vaughan Williams: Serenade to Music; Mahler: Symphony 2, Flint Symphony Orchestra, 2005-04-09 (Box: 13, Folder 23)
    - Verdi: Falstaff Act IV (Dame Quickly), Collegiate Chorale (Carnegie Hall), 2005-04-20 (Box: 13, Folder 24)
    - Mahler: Symphony 3, Huntsville Symphony Orchestra, 2005-05-07 (Box: 13, Folder 25)
    - Dvořák: Stabat Mater, Cincinnati May Festival, 2005-05-20 (Box: 13, Folder 26)
    - Blitzstein: Regina (Addie), American Symphony Orchestra, Summerscape 2005 (Bard College), 2005-07-2005-08 (Box: 13, Folder 27)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess (Maria), Washington National Opera (Kennedy Center), 2005-10-2005-11 (Box: 13, Folder 28)
    - Purcell and Brahms vocal music, Dame Myra Hess Memorial Concert, Chicago Cultural Center, 2005-12-22 (Box: 13, Folder 29)
    - Celebration of Life, Helen May Hopkins Ennis, Deliverance Evangelistic Church (Philadelphia, PA), 2006-11-25 (Box: 13, Folder 30)
    - Mozart: Requiem, St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, 2006-02 (Box: 14, Folder 1)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Huntsville Symphony Orchestra, 2006-02-25 (Box: 14, Folder 2)
    - Mahler: Das Liedvon der Erde, Pensacola Symphony Orchestra, 2006-03-04 (Box: 14, Folder 3)
    - Joplin: Treemonisha (Monisha), Collegiate Chorale Singers and Orchestra (Lincoln Center), 2006-03-09 (Box: 14, Folder 4)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Louisville Orchestra, 2006-03 (Box: 14, Folder 5)
    - Elgar: Sea Pictures, Louisville Orchestra, 2006-04-23 (Box: 14, Folder 6)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Phoenix Symphony, 2006-05 (Box: 14, Folder 7)
    - Bach Choir of Bethlehem 99th Annual Bach Festival, 2006-05-11 (Box: 14, Folder 8)
    - Let My People Go, Baltimore Choral Arts Society, 2006-10-29 (Box: 14, Folder 9)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess, Opera Pacific (Orange County Performing Arts Center), 2006-10 (Box: 14, Folder 10)
    - Handel: Messiah, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, 2006-09-12 (Box: 14, Folder 11)
    - Handel: Messiah, Nashville Symphony, 2006-12 (Box: 14, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Recital, Indiana University, 2007-01-14 (Box: 14, Folder 13)
    - Music and the Written Word, Indiana University, 2007-02-24 (Box: 14, Folder 13)
    - Indiana University Singing Hoosiers, 2007-03-31 (Box: 14, Folder 13)
    - Celebration of Academic Excellence, Indiana University, 2007-08-24 (Box: 14, Folder 13)
    - Indiana University Jazz Ensemble Inauguration Concert, 2007-10-21 (Box: 14, Folder 13)
    - The Great Spiritual Concert, Opera Birmingham, 2007-02-11 (Box: 14, Folder 14)
    - IU Presidential Inauguration Concert, IU Jazz Ensemble, 2007-10-21 (Box: 14, Folder 15)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, Bach Chorale Singers and Orchestra (Lafayette, IN), 2007-10-26 (Box: 14, Folder 16)
    - Toil and Triumph: A Celebration of the Spiritual, Singing City (First Baptist Church, Philadelphia, PA), 2007-11-10 (Box: 14, Folder 17)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Master Chorale of Washington (Kennedy Center), 2007-11-18 (Box: 14, Folder 18)
    - Vocal Masterclass, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society and Boyer College of Music and Dance, 2008-01-22 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - Celebration of the Spirituals, African American Choral Ensemble, Indiana University, 2008-01-27 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - AIT Winter Recital, Opera Theatre of St. Louis, 2008-02-10 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Recital, Indiana University, 2008-03-02 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - Settlement Music School Distinguished Alumni Series Recital (Philadelphia, PA), 2008-03-09 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - Holiday Celebration, Indiana University, 2008-12-01 (Box: 14, Folder 19)
    - Recital, Independence Seaport Museum, Philadelphia Chamber Music Society, 2008-01-25 (Box: 14, Folder 20)
    - A Tribute to Black Pioneers in Music, Performance and Masterclass, University of Colorado at Boulder, 2008-02-23-2008-02-24 (Box: 14, Folder 21)
    - Mendelssohn: Elijah, Hattiesburg Civic Chorus and Concert Association, 2008-04-05 (Box: 14, Folder 22)
    - Let My People Go, Master Chorale of Washington (Kennedy Center), 2008-04-20 (Box: 14, Folder 23)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess (Maria), Opera Birmingham and Alabama Symphony Orchestra, 2008-04 (Box: 14, Folder 24)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Nashville Symphony, 2008-05 (Box: 14, Folder 25)
    - Beethoven: Missa Solemnis, Singing City 60th Anniversary Concert (Bryn Mawr, PA), 2008-05-04 (Box: 14, Folder 26)
    - Eötvös: Of Love and Other Demons (Dominga), Glyndebourne Opera Festival (UK), 2008-08 (Box: 14, Folder 27)
    - Glyndebourne Opera Festival Program Book, 2008 (Box: 14, Folder 28)
    - Gershwin: Porgy and Bess (Maria), Lyric Opera of Chicago, 2008-11-2008-12 (Box: 14, Folder 29)
    - An Evening With IU Foundation Board of Directors and Special Guests, 2009-06-18 (Box: 14, Folder 30)
    - Indiana University Voice Faculty Cabaret, 2009-09-13 (Box: 14, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Recital for David Ward-Steinman, Indiana University, 2009-11-20 (Box: 14, Folder 30)
    - The Great Opera Gala, Opera Birmingham, 2009-01-24 (Box: 14, Folder 31)
    - Verdi: Requiem, Mendelssohn Club of Philadelphia, 2009-03-29 (Box: 14, Folder 32)
    - Baldwin-Wallace College Bach Festival, 2009-04 (Box: 14, Folder 33)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Columbus Symphony, 2009-10 (Box: 14, Folder 34)
    - Celebration of Spirituals (Committee Member), Indiana University, 2010-02-07 (Box: 15, Folder 1)
    - Berio: Folksongs for Mezzo-Soprano and Orchestra, Indiana University Symphony Orchestra, 2010-03-10 (Box: 15, Folder 1)
    - Bizet: Carmen Habanera, CAP Faculty Recital, 2010-07-26 (Box: 15, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Annual Lift Every Voice: A Celebration of the African American Spiritual, South Bend Symphonic Choir, Choral, and Gospel Ensemble, 2010-02-27 (Box: 15, Folder 1)
    - Joyful Sounds: Gospel Across America (Kennedy Center), 2010-04-21 (Box: 15, Folder 2)
    - Szymanowski: Stabat Mater, Radio Filharmonish Orkest (Concertgebouw, Amsterdam), 2010-06-05 (Box: 15, Folder 3)
    - Summertime Songs, Philadelphia Orchestra, 2010-06-22 (Box: 15, Folder 4)
    - Beethoven: Symphony No. 9, Boston Symphony Orchestra (Tanglewood), 2010-08-29 (Box: 15, Folder 5)
    - Handel: Messiah, Washington National Cathedral Choir and Baroque Orchestra, 2010-12 (Box: 15, Folder 6)
    - Handel: Messiah, First African Methodist Episcopal Church, Bethel Music Ministry (Harlem, NY), 2010-12-19 (Box: 15, Folder 7)
    - Benefit Concert for Japan, Indiana University, 2011-04-18 (Box: 15, Folder 8)
    - Holiday Celebration, Indiana University, 2011-10-06 (Box: 15, Folder 8)
    - Palm Sunday, Fairview United Methodist Church (Bloomington, IN), 2011-04-01 (Box: 15, Folder 8)
    - R. Schumann: Aus dem Hebräischen Gesängen; Copland: At the River, Ensemble Christo (IU Neal-Marshall Black Culture Center), 2011-11-06 (Box: 15, Folder 8)
    - Tippett: A Child of Our Time, Utah Symphony, 2011-04 (Box: 15, Folder 9)
    - Mahler: Symphony No. 2, Amarillo Symphony, 2011-04 (Box: 15, Folder 10)
    - Music Ministers with a Song and a Sword (Indianapolis, IN), 2011-04 (Box: 15, Folder 11)